# Alan Krajina



## **ABOUT ME**

Frontend developer with 2+ years of working experience using React and Svelte. Always thriving to create the cleanest and most efficient code that not only makes the app run great, but gives the client the most user friendly and eye catching UI.

Overall experience as a Fullstack creating services and it's relevant architecture in NodeJs and Golang.

### TECHNICAL PROJECTS

### **SOSELL** browser & mobile app

Digital Impact Awards 2020 winner Best development of proprietary social media platform and tools

https://www.communicatemagazine.com/news/2021/digital-impact-awards-2020-winners-announced/

Built using ReactJS and React Native expo. Utilizes latest features like React Hooks, TypeScript, Redux for state management, Deep Linking for navigation, Apollo GraphQL for queries and mutation, Material UI etc.

Other projects listed on my LinkedIn page.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **FLATIRON SCHOOL**

(2019 - 2020)

Full Stack Software Development Program JavaScript, React/Redux; Ruby on Rails

#### COLLEGE OF OCCUPATIONAL SAFETY AND HEALTH

Zagreb, Croatia (2010 – 2015) HSE Specialist Engineer

### **COURSES**

Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree
Udacity

React - The Complete Guide
React Native - The Practical Guide 2020
The Web Developer Bootcamp
Modern JavaScript (from Novice to Ninja)

Udemy

### CONTACT

+44 7907 448625

+385 91 736 6115

London, UK / Zagreb, Croatia

alankrajina88@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alankrajina/

https://github.com/AlanKrajina

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript - ES10/ES2019

ReactJS & React Native (hooks), Svelte

Redux, TypeScript, Cypress

Apollo, GraphQL, REST

Material UI. Storybook, Tailwind

GitKraken, Docker, JIRA

Junior React Developer mock interview with Skilled after finishing Flatiron School:

https://api.skilledinc.com/report-card/3349

### **EXPERIENCE**

Agent3: End-to-end ABM - LONDON, UK

Fullstack Developer (March 2020 - June 2022)

- Main responsibility development of all frontend aspects for 10+ apps created using React and Svelte
- Helping backend creating services using NodeJs and Go

#### APPLE - CORK, IRELAND

OS & MacOS Tech Support (June 2018 - Dec 2018)

iOS Technical Support (June 2017 - June 2018)

- Resolving end user technical issues that requires advanced knowledge of Mac or iOS systems.
- Continuously accomplishing above 90% target req (given promotion to MacOS).